const data = [
    {
        question: "What is the name of Thor’s hammer?",
        option1: "Vanir",
        option2: "Mjolnir",
        option3: "Aesir",
        option4: "Norn",
        ans: "Mjolnir"
        //exp:""
    },
    {
        question: "In the Incredible Hulk, what does Tony tell Thaddeus Ross at the end of the film?",
        option1: "That he wants to study The Hulk",
        option2: "That he knows about S.H.I.E.L.D.",
        option3: "That they are putting a team together",
        option4: "That Thaddeus owes him money",
        ans: "That they are putting a team together"
        //exp:""
    },
    {
        question: "What is Captain America’s shield made of?",
        option1: "Adamantium",
        option2: "Promethium",
        option3: "Vibranium",
        option4: "Carbonadium",
        ans: "Vibranium"
        //exp:""
    },
    {
        question: "The Flerkens are a race of extremely dangerous aliens that resembles what?",
        option1: "Cats",
        option2: "Ducks",
        option3: "Reptiles",
        option4: "Raccoons",
        ans: "Cats"
        //exp:""
    },
    {
        question: "Before becoming Vision, what is the name of Iron Man’s A.I. butler?",
        option1: "H.O.M.E.R.",
        option2: "J.A.R.V.I.S.",
        option3: "A.L.F.R.E.D.",
        option4: "M.A.R.V.I.N.",
        ans: "J.A.R.V.I.S."
        //exp:""
    },
    {
        question: "What is the real name of the Black Panther?",
        option1: "T’Challa",
        option2: "M’Baku",
        option3: "N’Jadaka",
        option4: "N’Jobu",
        ans: "T’Challa"
        //exp:""
    },
    {
        question: "What is the alien race Loki sends to invade Earth in The Avengers?",
        option1: "The Chitauri",
        option2: "The Skrulls",
        option3: "The Kree",
        option4: "The Flerkens",
        ans: "The Chitauri"
        //exp:""
    },
    {
        question: "Who was the last holder of the Space Stone before Thanos claims it for his Infinity Gauntlet?",
        option1: "Thor",
        option2: "Loki",
        option3: "The Collector",
        option4: "Tony Stark",
        ans: "Loki"
        //exp:""
    },
    {
        question: "What fake name does Natasha use when she first meets Tony?",
        option1: "Natalie Rushman",
        option2: "Natalia Romanoff",
        option3: "Nicole Rohan",
        option4: "Naya Rabe",
        ans: "Natalie Rushman"
        //exp:""
    },
    {
        question: "What does Thor want another of when he’s in the diner?",
        option1: "slice of pie",
        option2: "pint of beer",
        option3: "stack of pancakes",
        option4: "cup of coffee",
        ans: "cup of coffee"
        //exp:""
    },
    {
        question: "Where does Peggy tell Steve she wants to meet him for a dance, before he plunges into the ice?",
        option1: "The Cotton Club",
        option2: "The Stork Club",
        option3: "El Morocco",
        option4: "The Copacabana",
        ans: "The Stork Club"
        //exp:""
    },
    {
        question: "About which city do Hawkeye and Black Widow often reminisce?",
        option1: "Budapest",
        option2: "Prague",
        option3: "Istanbul",
        option4: "Sokovia",
        ans: "Budapest"
        //exp:""
    },
    {
        question: "Who is killed by Loki in the Avengers?",
        option1: "Maria Hill",
        option2: "Nick Fury",
        option3: "Agent Coulson",
        option4: "Doctor Erik Selvig",
        ans: "Agent Coulson"
        //exp:""
    },
    {
        question: "Who is Black Panther’s sister?",
        option1: "Shuri",
        option2: "Nakia",
        option3: "Ramonda",
        option4: "Okoye",
        ans: "Shuri"
        //exp:""
    },
    {
        question: "Who does the Mad Titan sacrifice to acquire the Soul Stone?",
        option1: "Nebula",
        option2: "Ebony Maw",
        option3: "Cull Obsidian",
        option4: "Gamora",
        ans: "Gamora"
        //exp:""
    }
];

module.exports = data;